Guide to the Ted Fagan Collection
Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound
- Reel to reel tapes
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Manon Lescaut 1959, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 230)
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Manon Lescaut 1959, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 231)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Acts I and II1959, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 232)
    Nilsson, Birgit as Isolde; Vickers, Jon as Tristan. Metropolitan Opera Company
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Act III1959, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 233)
  - Kodály, Zoltán, 1882-1967. Székely fonó, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 234)
    Tiszay, Magda as the lady of the house; Palló, Imre, 1941- as the suitor; Uher, Zita as the neighbor; Szecsödy, Irén as a young girl; Edwardy, Tibor as a young lad; Rösler, Endre as the bignosed flea. Symphony Orchestra and Chorus of Radio Budapest. Czech production.
  - Kodály, Zoltán, 1882-1967. Székely fonó, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 235)
  - Kodály, Zoltán, 1882-1967. Székely fonó, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 236)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Infedeltà delusa. Trinche vaine, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 237)
    László, Margit as Vestina; Faragó, András as Nanni; Palscó, Sándor as Nencio; Réti, József as Philippo; Lorenz, Kornélia as Sandrina; Lukács, Ervin, conductor; Huszár, Klára, producer
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Infedeltà delusa. Trinche vaine, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 238)
  - Haydn, Joseph, 1732-1809. Infedeltà delusa. Trinche vaine, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 239)
  - United Nations. New Zealand Reception. Part I1957, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 240)
  - Chabrier, Emmanuel, 1841-1894. Education manquée 1957, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 241)
  - Chabrier, Emmanuel, 1841-1894. Education manquée 1957, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 242)
    "Treasury of the 78: a program of important recorded performances not as yet reissued." Orchestra Symphonique de Paris. Bruck, Charles, conductor
  - Polish United Nations Concert. Part VNov. 28, 1955, 5" reel (Box 13, Folder 243)
  - United Nations. New Zealand Reception. Part II1957, 5" reel (Box 13, Folder 244)
  - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Moses und Aron, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 245)
    Fiedler, Hans Herbert as Moses; Krebs, Helmut as Aaron; Steingruber-Wildgans, Ilone, young girl; Zollenkopf, Ursula as an invalid woman; Kretschmar, Helmut as a naked youth; Günter, Horst, 1913- as another man; Rieth, Hermann as a priest. As naked virgins: Förster-Georgi, Dorothea; Pfeffer-Düring, Carla Maria; Tammun, Anna Maria; Bettke, Charlotte. As solo voices in the orchestra: Förster-Georgi, Dorothea, soprano; Hüger, Maria, mezzo-sopran; Zollenkopf, Ursula, alto; Stuckmann, Hartig, tenor; Sellenpin, Horst, baritone; Lühr, Ernest-Max, bass. Chorus of the Hamburg Academy of Music; Chorus and Orchestra of the Norddeutscher Rundfunk. Rosbaud, Hans, 1895-1962, conductor
  - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Moses und Aron, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 246)
  - Schoenberg, Arnold, 1874-1951. Moses und Aron, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 247)
  - Chaliapin, Fyodor Ivanovich, 1873-1938, bass, 5" reel (Box 13, Folder 248)
  - WBAI Radio Station. Interview with Sherry and Fagan, 5" reel (Box 13, Folder 249)
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème Mar.11, 1961, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 250)
    Metropolitan Opera Company
  - Lehmann, Lotte, soprano, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 251)
    (Taped from discs) Lieder and opera selections
  - London Hoffnung Festival. Part I, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 252)
  - Anonymous Singers, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 253)
  - Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Lied von der Erde, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 254)
    (Taped from discs) Thorborg, Kerstin, 1896-1970, mezzo-soprano; Kullman, Charles, 1903-1983, tenor
  - The United Nations and the Luis Calvo McKennan Hospital in Santiago, Chile., 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 255)
    Theodore Fagan describes the role of the Center for the Care of Premature babies.
  - Bass Baritones, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 256)
  - Contraltos and mezzo-sopranos, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 257)
  - Tenors, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 258)
  - Sopranos I, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 259)
  - Sopranos II, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 260)
  - Tenors, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 261)
  - Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 262)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Orfeo I, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 263)
  - Monteverdi, Claudio, 1567-1643. Orfeo II, 7" reel (Box 13, Folder 264)
  - Berlioz, Hector, 1803-1869. Mort d'Orphée, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 265)
  - Sopranos I, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 266)
  - Sopranos II, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 267)
  - Tenors, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 268)
  - Mezzo-Sopranos and Contraltos, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 269)
  - Sopranos I, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 270)
  - Sopranos II, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 271)
  - Ensembles, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 272)
  - United Nations. Human Rights Day1958, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 273)
    Tebaldi, Renata, soprano
  - Tenors, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 274)
  - Sopranos I, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 275)
  - Sopranos II, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 276)
  - Mezzo-Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 277)
  - Tenors I, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 278)
  - Tenors II, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 279)
  - Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 280)
  - Mezzo-Sopranos, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 281)
  - Schumann, Elisabeth, soprano, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 282)
  - Duets, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 283)
  - Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Adriana Lecouvreur 1951, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 284)
    An off the air recording from Palacio de Bellas Artes, Mexico City. Petrella, Clara, 1914-1987, soprano; Del Monaco, Mario, 1915-1982, tenor; Domínguez, Oralia, contralto; Taddei, Giuseppe, baritone; Silva, Roberto, 1909-1965, bass.
  - Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly May 29, 1951, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 285)
    An off the air recording from Palacio de Bellas Artes, Mexico City. González, Irma, soprano; Domínguez, Oralia, contralto; Del Monaco, Mario, 1915-1982, tenor; Morelli, Carlo, 1897-1970, baritone. Chorus and Orchestra of the Palacio de Bellas Artes, Mexico
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda 1958, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 286)
    Atzimba, Mexico. Castro, Ricardo. Second scene of the act IV.
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda 1958, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 287)
  - Vocal. Various from Mexico, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 288)
    Cortis, Antonio, 1891-1952, tenor; Toniolo, Rhea, alto. Saint-Saëns, Camille, 1835-1921. Samson et Dalila. Mon c ur s'ouvre à ta voix -- Cortis, Antonio, 1891-1952, tenor. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera. Di' tu se fedele -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Andrea Chénier. Credo a una possanza -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Trittico. Gianni Schicchi. Firenze è come un albero fiorito -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Amico Fritz. O amore, o bella luce del core -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Fanciulla del West. Or son sei mesi -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Ah, sì, ben mio; Rigoletto. Questa o quella per me pari sono -- Granforte, Apollo, baritone. Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Chanson du toréador -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Avant de quitter ces lieux -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Bohème. O Mimì, tu più non torni -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Forza del destino. Solenne in quest'ora; Rigoletto. Pari siamo!; Rigoletto. È il sol dell'anima; Granforte, Apollo, baritone; Zaccarini, Franco, bass. Duet: Signor, va non ho niente; Otello. Selection -- Zenatello, Giovanni, 1876-1949, tenor. Otello. Sì, pel ciel marmoreo giuro! -- Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tannhäuser. O du mein holder Abendstern -- Albani, Carlo, tenor. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Miserere; Deserto sulla terra -- Renaud, Maurice, 1861-1933, baritone. Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Favorite -- Léonor, viens -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Soir -- Granforte, Apollo, baritone. Rossini, Gioacchino, 1792-1868. Barbiere di Siviglia. Largo al factotum -- Minghini-Cattaneo, Irene, 1892-1944, alto; Granforte, Apollo, baritone. Ponchielli, Amilcare, 1834-1886. Gioconda. Figlia, che reggi il tremulo piè; Voce di donna o d'angelo -- Monti, Hilda, soprano; Granforte, Apollo, baritone; Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Ciel! mio padre! -- Tokatyan, Armand, 1894-1960, tenor. Massenet, Jules, 1842-1912. Manon. Ah! fuyez, douce image -- Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Salut, demeure chaste et pure -- Buzzi-Peccia, Arturo, 1854-1943. Lolita -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Ultima canzone -- Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Cavalleria rusticana. Viva il vino spumeggiante -- Giordano, Umberto, 1867-1948. Fedora. Amor ti vieta -- Pérez Freire, Osmán, 1880-1930. Ay, ay, ay -- Capua, Rinaldo di. O sole mio -- Bori, Lucrezia, 1887-1960, soprano; Fleta, Miguel, 1897-1938, tenor. Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Parle-moi de ma mère -- Rozsa, Anna, 1898-1987, soprano; Pertile, Aureliano, 1885-1952, tenor. Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Amico Fritz. Suzel, buon dì -- Embil, Pepita Josefa, soprano; Rozsa, Anna, 1898-1987, soprano. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly. Un bel dì, vedremo -- Embil, Pepita Josefa, soprano. Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Ave Maria (Vocal version) -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Manon Lescaut. Donna non vidi mai -- Bassi, Amedeo, 1874-1949, tenor. Panizza, Ettore. Aurora. Inno a la bandiera
  - Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Don Pasquale, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 289)
    Mexico City
  - Vocals. Various from Mexican Broadcasts, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 290)
    Selections from off-the-air recordings of "Concierto General Motors," a television program originated in Mexico City, from April - Dec. 1952. Di Stefano, Giuseppe, 1921-, tenor. Trad. Dicitencello Vuje -- Mamma mia che vo sapé -- Vaga luna che irargenti -- Chi se noe scorda cchiu -- Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Fleur que tu m'avais jetée -- Core 'ngrato -- González, Irma, soprano. Ponce, Manuel M. (Manuel María), 1882-1948. Estrellita -- Trad. Goin' home -- Guajardo, Verdad Luz, soprano. Delibes, Léo. Passe pe -- Thomas, Ambroise, 1811-1896. Mignon. Je suis Titania -- Guerra Morgain, Amparo, soprano. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Tosca. Vissi d'arte -- Trad. Voci di Primavera -- Avedaño, Hugo, baritone. Denza, Luigi. Funiculì funiculà -- Domínguez, Oralia, mezzo-soprano. Bizet, Georges, 1838-1875. Carmen. Près des remparts de Séville; Habanera -- Cilèa, Francesco, 1866-1950. Arlesiana. È la solita storia -- Puig, Carlos, tenor. Quintero. Morucha -- Pérez Uribe de Rivera, Graciela, soprano. Donizetti, Gaetano, 1797-1848. Lucia di Lammermoor. Ardon gl'incensi -- Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Rigoletto. Caro nome; Puig, Carlos, tenor. Donna è mobile -- Rivera, Graciela. Ponce, Manuel M. (Manuel María), 1882-1948. Estrellita -- di Stefano, Giuseppe, tenor. Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Nessun dorma -- de Curtis. Tu ça non chiagne -- Barrera, Tomás, 1870-1938. Emigrantes. Granadinas -- Ponce, Manuel M. (Manuel María), 1882-1948. Estrellita -- Tosti, F. Paolo (Francesco Paolo), 1846-1916. Marechiare. The following is a Filippeschi, Mario recital from Dutch Columbia LP Record QC 5029 which contains: Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Nessun dorma - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Otello. Ora e per sempre addio -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Fanciulla del West. Ch'ella mi creda libero e lontano - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Trovatore. Ah, sì, ben mio; Di quella pira; Forza del destino. O tu che in seno agli angeli -- Meyerbeer, Giacomo, 1791-1864. Huguenots. Plus blanche que la blanche hermine -- Baldisseri, Nerina, sopran; Gigli, Beniamino, 1890-1957, tenor. Mascagni, Pietro, 1863-1945. Amico Fritz. Suzel, buon dì -- Zamboni, Maria, 1896-1976, soprano; Gigli, Beniamino, 1890-1957, tenor. Gounod, Charles, 1818-1893. Faust. Il se fait tard -- Giraldoni, Eugenio, 1871-1924, baritone. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Quest'assisa ch'io vesto
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Ballo in maschera, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 291)
    González, Irma as Amelia. Mexico City performance.
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Liebestod, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 292)
    Alsen, Elsa, 1880-1975, soprano
  - Lehmann, Lotte Master Classes, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 293)
  - Bloch, Ernest, 1880-1959. Schelomo, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 294)
    Nelsova, Zara, violoncello
  - Farrell, Eileen, 1920-2002, soprano, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 295)
    Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Beau soir -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Madama Butterfly. Ancora un passo -- Debussy, Claude, 1862-1918. Noël des enfants qui n'ont plus de maisons -- Poulenc, Francis, 1899-1963. Songs for Le bestiaire (Apollinaire), 1919, unpubd: Le boeuf, La mouche, La tortue, Le serpent, La colombe -- Puccini, Giacomo, 1858-1924. Turandot. Tu che di gel sei cinta; In questa reggia -- with Schipa, Tito, 1889-1965, tenor. Menotti, Gian Carlo, 1911- Consul. To this we've come
  - Tourel, Jennie, mezzo-soprano (Tape missing), 5" reel (Box 14, Folder 297)
    Mahler, Gustav, 1860-1911. Symphonies, no. 2, C minor. Urlicht. In memory of Mitropoulos, Dimitri, 1896-1960
  - Robinson, F. about Farrar, Geraldine, 1882-1967. Dec. 30, 1960, 5" reel (Box 14, Folder 298)
  - In Memoriam, Hammarskjöld, Dag, 1905-1961Dec. 30, 1960, 5" reel (Box 14, Folder 299)
    Narrated, written and produced by Pittendrigh, Ken
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro 1960, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 300)
    Fischer-Dieskau, Dietrich, 1925- as Count Almaviva; Della Casa, Lisa as Countess Almaviva; Kunz, Erich, 1909-1995 as Figaro; Seefried, Irmgard as Susana; Murray, Dickie as Basilio; Ludwig, Christa as Cherubino; Pernerstorfer, Alois, 1912-1978 as Bartolo; Rössl-Majdan, Hilde as Marcellina; Pantscheff, Ljubomir, 1913- as the uncle; Maikl, Liselotte as Barbarina; Majkut, Erich as Don Curzio; Forst, Erna as the first bridesmaid; Fleischmann, Anneliese, as the second bridesmaid. Wiener Philharmoniker and Konzertvereinigung Wiener Staatsopernchor. Böhm, Karl, 1868-1944.
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro 1960, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 301)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro 1960, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 302)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Nozze di Figaro 1960, 7" reel (Box 14, Folder 303)
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 304)
    Zaccaria, Nicola as a monk (Emperor Karl V); Christoff, Boris as Philipp II, King of Spain; Fernandi, Eugenio as Don Carlos, Prince of Spain; Bastianini, Ettore as Rodrigo, Marquis von Posa; Schmidt, Carlo as Count Lerma; Arié, Raffaele as the great inquisitor; Jurinac, Sena, 1921- as Elisabeth von Valois; Resnik, Regina, 1922- as Princess Eboli; Maikl, Liselotte as Marquesa von Mondekar; Balatsch, Norbert as Tebaldo; Bernhofer, Irene as Countess Aremberg; Klinke, Klaus as a royal Herald; Maikl, Liselotte as a voice from heaven. Wiener Philharmoniker and Konzertvereinigung Wiener Staatsopernchor. Santi, Nello, conductor
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 305)
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 306)
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 307)
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 308)
  - Salzburg Festival. Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Don Carlos 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 309)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act I, part 1 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 310)
    Schwarzkopf, Elisabeth as Fiordiligi; Ludwig, Christa as Dorabella; Prey, Hermann, 1929-1998 as Guglielmo; Kmentt, Waldemar as Ferrando; Sciutti, Graziella as Despina; Dönch, Karl as Don Alfonso. Wiener Philharmoniker and Konzertvereinigung Wiener Staatsopernchor. Böhm, Karl, 1894-1981, conductor
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act I, part 2 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 311)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act I, part 3 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 312)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act II, part 1 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 313)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act II, part 2 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 314)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Così fan tutte. Act II, part 3 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 315)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Finta semplice. Part I 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 316)
    Mazura, Franz as Cassandro; Wohlfahrt, Erwin as Polidoro; Casoni, Bianca Maria as Giacinta; Mathis, Edith as Ninetta; Schmidt, Manfred as Fracasso; Prohaska, Peter as Simone; Hallstein, Ingeborg as Rosina. Camerata Academica Salzburg. Conz, Bernhard, conductor
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Finta semplice. Part II 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 317)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. Part I1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 318)
    Wunderlich, Fritz, 1930-1966 as Tamino; Otto, Lisa as first lady; Plümacher, Hetty, 1922- as second lady; Wagner, Sieglinde as third lady; Berry, Walter as Papageno; Koth, Erika as Queen of the Night; Fölser, Liselotte as Pamina; Marschner, Kurt as Monostatos; Majkut, Erich as the first priest; Pantscheff, Ljubomir, 1913-, as the second priest; Frick, Gottlob, 1906-1994 as Sarastro; Sciutti, Graziella as Papagena. Wunderlich, Fritz, 1930-1966, speaker; Armored men: Charlebois, Robert; Pernertstoffer, Alois; Three boys: members from the Wiener Sängerknaben. Wiener Philharmoniker and Konzertvereinigung Wiener Staatsopernchor. Keiberth, Joseph, conductor
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. Part II1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 319)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. Part III1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 320)
  - Salzburg Festival. Mozart, Wolfgang Amadeus, 1756-1791. Zauberflöte. Part IV1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 321)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Rheingold. Part I 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 322)
    Uhde, Hermann, 1914-1965 as Wotan; Stewart, Thomas, 1928-2006 as Donner; Paskuda, Georg as Froh; Stolze, Gerhard as Loge; Töpper, Hertha as Fricka; Bjoner, Ingrid as Freia; Kraus, Otakar, 1909-1980 as Alberich; Kraus, Harold as Mime; Mill, Arnold van as Fasolt; Kroh, Peter as Fafner; Höffgen, Marga as Erda; Siebert, Dorothea as Woglinde; Hellman, Claudia as Wellgunde; Cervaná, Sona as Flosshilde. Bayreuther Festspiele. Orchester. Kempe, Rudolph, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Rheingold. Part II 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 323)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Rheingold. Part III 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 324)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Rheingold. Part IV1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 325)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 326)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 327)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 328)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 329)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 330)
  - Tape and index card mising, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 331)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part I 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 332)
    Hopf, Hans as Siegfried; Kraus, Harold as Mime; Uhde, Hermann, 1914-1965 as the wanderer; Kraus, Otakar, 1909-1980 as Alberich; Kroh, Peter as Fafner; Nilsson, Birgit as Brunnhilde; Höffgen, Marga as Erda; Siebert, Dorothea as Waldvogel. Bayreuther Festspiele. Orchester. Kempe, Rudolph, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part II 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 333)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part III 1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 334)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part IV1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 335)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part V1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 336)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part VI1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 337)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part VII1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 338)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Siegfried. Part VIII1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 339)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part I1960, 7" reel (Box 15, Folder 340)
    Hopf, Hans as Siegfried; Stewart, Thomas, 1928-2006 as Gunther; Frick, Gottlob, 1906-1994 as Hagen; Kraus, Otakar, 1909-1980 as Alberich; Nilsson, Birgit as Brünnhilde; Bjoner, Ingrid as Gutrune; Hoffman, Grace as Waltraute; Three Norns: Siewert, Ruth; Hoffman, Grace; Nordmo Løvberg, Åse; Siebert, Dorothea as Woglinde; Hellman, Claudia as Wellgunde; Cervaná, Soma as Flosshilde. Bayreuther Festspiele. Orchester. Kempe, Rudolph, conductor
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part II1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 341)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part III1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 342)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part IV1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 343)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part V1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 344)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part VI1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 345)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part VII1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 346)
  - Bayreuther Festspiele. Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Ring des Nibelungen. Götterdämmerung Part VIII 1960, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 347)
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Part IMar. 18, 1961, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 348)
    Metropolitan Opera performance
  - Wagner, Richard, 1813-1883. Tristan und Isolde. Part IIMar. 18, 1961, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 349)
  - Offenbach, Jacques, 1819-1880. Périchole Mar. 22, ?, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 350)
    Lafaye, Suzanne as Perichole; Noguera, Louis as the viceroy. Markevitch, Igor, 1912-1983, conductor. From a French Columbia recording not available in the US
  - Loneliness. A documentary program from WBAI, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 351)
    Tape missing
  - Pic Nic at the UN, 5" reel (Box 16, Folder 353)
    Composite of Cuban riots
  - Unicorn Concert Orchestra. Horn Fanfares, 5" reel (Box 16, Folder 354)
  - Biographies in Music. Radio Program. The Ponselle Sisters., 5" reel (Box 16, Folder 355)
    Ponselle, Carmela, 1892-1977 and Ponselle, Rosa, 1897-1981
  - Ustinov, Peter in two sketches., 3" reel (Box 16, Folder 356)
    British-born actor, writer, dramatist and raconteur
  - Verdi, Giuseppe, 1813-1901. Aïda. Excerpts Dec. 15, 1962, 5" reel (Box 16, Folder 357)
    Bergonzi, Carlo, tenor
  - Muzio, Claudia, 1889-1936 on Edisons, 5" reel (Box 16, Folder 358)
    Catalani, Alfredo, 1854-1893. Wally. Ebben? Ne andrò lontana -- Leoncavallo, Ruggiero, 1858-1919. Pagliacci. Selection -- Gluck, Christoph Willibald, Ritter von, 1714-1787. Paride ed Elena. Spiagge amate -- Tchaikovsky, Peter Ilich, 1840-1893. Eugene Onegin. Letter scene
  - Teyte, Maggie, 1888-1976, soprano, 7" reel (Box 16, Folder 359)